const pageSize = 20

var pageOne = {"items":[{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_118","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Initialize an array of arrays","answer":"$myarray=array ( array (a11,a12), array (a21,a22) );","highlight":{"question":["Initialize an <em>array</em> of <em>arrays</em>"],"answer":["$myarray=<em>array</em> ( <em>array</em> (a11,a12), <em>array</em> (a21,a22) );"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_111","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Initialize an empty array","answer":"$myarray=array();","highlight":{"question":["Initialize an empty <em>array</em>"],"answer":["$myarray=<em>array</em>();"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_175","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Separate string in array elements using regular expression example: separator is @ or .","answer":"$array=split(\"\"\\.|@\"\",$inputstring);","highlight":{"question":["Separate string in <em>array</em> elements using regular expression example: separator is @ or ."],"answer":["$<em>array</em>=split(\"\"\\.|@\"\",$inputstring);"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_110","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Initialize an array","answer":"$myarray=array(value1,...);","highlight":{"question":["Initialize an <em>array</em>"],"answer":["$myarray=<em>array</em>(value1,...);"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_116","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Initialize an array with keys","answer":"$myarray=array(key1=>value1,key2=>value2,...);","highlight":{"question":["Initialize an <em>array</em> with keys"],"answer":["$myarray=<em>array</em>(key1=>value1,key2=>value2,...);"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_119","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Sort an array","answer":"sort($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Sort an <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_290","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Condition: is the array empty","answer":"myArray.isEmpty()","highlight":{"question":["Condition: is the <em>array</em> empty"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_114","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Show the content of the array","answer":"print_r($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Show the content of the <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_115","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Use each element of the array","answer":"foreach ( $myarray as $variable ) { echo $variable; ","highlight":{"question":["Use each element of the <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_169","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Give array of strings matching the expression","answer":"$result=preg_match($expression,$inputstring,$arrayoffound);","highlight":{"question":["Give <em>array</em> of strings matching the expression"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_291","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Condition: does the array contains an object","answer":"myArray.contains(myObject)","highlight":{"question":["Condition: does the <em>array</em> contains an object"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_300","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get the last element of a stort array","answer":"myObject=myArray.last();","highlight":{"question":["Get the last element of a stort <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_298","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get the first element of a sorted array","answer":"myObject=myArray.first();","highlight":{"question":["Get the first element of a sorted <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_293","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get the nth element of an array","answer":"myObject=myArray.get(n);","highlight":{"question":["Get the nth element of an <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_224","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Logic","question":"Loop through a bidimensional array of int","answer":"for (int currentable[] : mybimensionaltable){ for ( int currentvalue : currentable ){ use currentvalue ","highlight":{"question":["Loop through a bidimensional <em>array</em> of int"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_148","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Convert back array to string (delimiter ;)","answer":"implode(';',$myarray)","highlight":{"question":["Convert back <em>array</em> to string (delimiter ;)"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_132","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Number of elements in an array","answer":"count($myarray) or sizeof($myarray)","highlight":{"question":["Number of elements in an <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_131","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Modify each element of an array using a function multiplying by 3 each element in the array","answer":"function mymodificator(&$inputvalue,$mykey,$myvalue) { $inputvalue*=$myvalue; ","highlight":{"question":["Modify each element of an <em>array</em> using a function multiplying by 3 each element in the <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_124","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Put a random order in elements of the array","answer":"shuffle($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Put a random order in elements of the <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_126","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Take of the last element of an array","answer":"array_pop($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Take of the last element of an <em>array</em>"]}}],"details":{"totalHits":47,"aggregations":{"category":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"PHP","doc_count":25,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Deal with arrays","doc_count":21},{"key":"Deal with strings","doc_count":4}]}},{"key":"JAVA","doc_count":22,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Dealing with Arrays","doc_count":19},{"key":"Data types, variables and tables","doc_count":1},{"key":"Dealing with Strings","doc_count":1},{"key":"Logic","doc_count":1}]}}]}}}}

var pageTwo = {"items":[{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_147","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Convert string to array, using ;as delimiter","answer":"explode(';',$input)","highlight":{"question":["Convert string to <em>array</em>, using ;as delimiter"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_121","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Array with keys and values: sort per values","answer":"asort($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["<em>Array</em> with keys and values: sort per values"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_287","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Add an element in an array of objects","answer":"booleanResult=myArray.add(myObject);","highlight":{"question":["Add an element in an <em>array</em> of objects"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_125","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Add an element at the end of an array","answer":"array_push($myarray,$myelement);","highlight":{"question":["Add an element at the end of an <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_212","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Data types, variables and tables","question":"Declare and initialize a two dimension array of integers","answer":"int my_table[][]=new int[mysizex][mysizey]","highlight":{"question":["Declare and initialize a two dimension <em>array</em> of integers"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_289","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Delete all elements in an array of objects","answer":"myArray.add(myObject);","highlight":{"question":["Delete all elements in an <em>array</em> of objects"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_120","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Array with keys and values: sort per keys","answer":"ksort($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["<em>Array</em> with keys and values: sort per keys"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_112","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Make an array containing numbers from 1 to 10","answer":"$mylist=range(1,10);","highlight":{"question":["Make an <em>array</em> containing numbers from 1 to 10"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_113","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Access first element of the array and put in a variable","answer":"$myelement=$myarray[0];","highlight":{"question":["Access first element of the <em>array</em> and put in a variable"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_117","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Use each element of the array, get keys and values","answer":"foreach ( $myarray as $key=> $value ) { echo $key.\"\" : \"\".$value; ","highlight":{"question":["Use each element of the <em>array</em>, get keys and values"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_302","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get an array of object between object1 and object2","answer":"myNewArray=myArray.subSet(firstObject,lastObject); lastObject is not included","highlight":{"question":["Get an <em>array</em> of object between object1 and object2"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_299","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get an array of object lesser than an object","answer":"myNewArray=myArray.headSet(myObject);","highlight":{"question":["Get an <em>array</em> of object lesser than an object"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_286","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Interface related to array of objects with the minimum functionality to handle the array: add an element, clear, check if empty, get size","answer":"Interface is Collection","highlight":{"question":["Interface related to <em>array</em> of objects with the minimum functionality to handle the <em>array</em>: add an element"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_301","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get an array of object equal or greater than an object","answer":"myNewArray=myArray.tailSet(myObject);","highlight":{"question":["Get an <em>array</em> of object equal or greater than an object"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_128","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Get the next element in an array and stay on this position","answer":"$myvalue=next($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Get the next element in an <em>array</em> and stay on this position"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_306","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Create an array of object with the possibility to use fifo functionality","answer":"Interface is queue: Can use LinkedList: LinkedList myArray=new LinkendList","highlight":{"question":["Create an <em>array</em> of object with the possibility to use fifo functionality"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_129","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Get the previous element in an array and stay on this position","answer":"$myvalue=prev($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Get the previous element in an <em>array</em> and stay on this position"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_130","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Get the first element of an array and stay on this position","answer":"$myvalue=reset($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Get the first element of an <em>array</em> and stay on this position"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_127","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with arrays","question":"Get the last element of an array and stay on this position","answer":"$myvalue=end($myarray);","highlight":{"question":["Get the last element of an <em>array</em> and stay on this position"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_261","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Strings","question":"Take characters from position i to j of a string and put in an array of character, putting the first character at position k in this array","answer":"myString.getChars(i,j,myArrayOfChars,k)","highlight":{"question":["Take characters from position i to j of a string and put in an <em>array</em> of character, putting the first","character at position k in this <em>array</em>"]}}],"details":{"totalHits":47,"aggregations":{"category":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"PHP","doc_count":25,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Deal with arrays","doc_count":21},{"key":"Deal with strings","doc_count":4}]}},{"key":"JAVA","doc_count":22,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Dealing with Arrays","doc_count":19},{"key":"Data types, variables and tables","doc_count":1},{"key":"Dealing with Strings","doc_count":1},{"key":"Logic","doc_count":1}]}}]}}}}

var pageThree = {"items":[{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_296","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Create an array of objects with the ability to keep the objects in sequence and not accepting duplicates","answer":"Interface is Set Can use HashSet for very big arrays - uses a hash table HashSet myArray=new HashSet(); Can use LinkedHashSet to return sequences of objects. LinkedHashSet myArray=new LinkedHashSet();","highlight":{"question":["Create an <em>array</em> of objects with the ability to keep the objects in sequence and not accepting duplicates"],"answer":["Interface is Set Can use HashSet for very big <em>arrays</em> - uses a hash table HashSet myArray=new HashSet("]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_307","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Create an array of object with the possibility to use bidirectional fifo functionality ( fifo + lifo )","answer":"Interface is Deque Can use class ArrayDeque","highlight":{"question":["Create an <em>array</em> of object with the possibility to use bidirectional fifo functionality ( fifo + lifo"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_292","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Create an array of objects with the ability to keep the objects in sequence and so for instance get the position of an element","answer":"Interface is List ArrayList myArray=new ArrayList(); The size of ArrayList augments automatically, but you can use myArray.ensureCapacity(n) to augment the capacity myArray.trimToSize() to reduce it to the minimum necessary to keep the existing elements in the array","highlight":{"question":["Create an <em>array</em> of objects with the ability to keep the objects in sequence and so for instance get the"],"answer":["capacity myArray.trimToSize() to reduce it to the minimum necessary to keep the existing elements in the <em>array</em>"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_303","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Create an array of object with the possibility to check with objects are the closest match to a given object","answer":"NavigableSet myArray=","highlight":{"question":["Create an <em>array</em> of object with the possibility to check with objects are the closest match to a given"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_294","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get the position of the first occurence of an object in an array of object. What is the value if the object is not found","answer":"position=myArray.indexOf(object); if nothing is found, position is -1","highlight":{"question":["Get the position of the first occurence of an object in an <em>array</em> of object."]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_295","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Get the position of the first occurence of an object in an array of object. What is the value if the object is not found","answer":"position=myArray.lastIndexOf(object); if nothing is found, position is -1","highlight":{"question":["Get the position of the first occurence of an object in an <em>array</em> of object."]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_297","category":"JAVA","subCategory":"Dealing with Arrays","question":"Create an array of objects with the ability to keep the objects in sequence, not accepting duplicates and sorting elements inside ( as a result, you can return elements greater than a value)","answer":"Interface is SortedSet Can use TreeSet that gives instant access to lists of ordered data TreeSet myArray=new TreeSet();","highlight":{"question":["Create an <em>array</em> of objects with the ability to keep the objects in sequence, not accepting duplicates"]}}],"details":{"totalHits":47,"aggregations":{"category":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"PHP","doc_count":25,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Deal with arrays","doc_count":21},{"key":"Deal with strings","doc_count":4}]}},{"key":"JAVA","doc_count":22,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Dealing with Arrays","doc_count":19},{"key":"Data types, variables and tables","doc_count":1},{"key":"Dealing with Strings","doc_count":1},{"key":"Logic","doc_count":1}]}}]}}}}

var filteredResult = {"items":[{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_175","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Separate string in array elements using regular expression example: separator is @ or .","answer":"$array=split(\"\"\\.|@\"\",$inputstring);","highlight":{"question":["Separate string in <em>array</em> elements using regular expression example: separator is @ or ."],"answer":["$<em>array</em>=split(\"\"\\.|@\"\",$inputstring);"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_169","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Give array of strings matching the expression","answer":"$result=preg_match($expression,$inputstring,$arrayoffound);","highlight":{"question":["Give <em>array</em> of strings matching the expression"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_148","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Convert back array to string (delimiter ;)","answer":"implode(';',$myarray)","highlight":{"question":["Convert back <em>array</em> to string (delimiter ;)"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_147","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Convert string to array, using ;as delimiter","answer":"explode(';',$input)","highlight":{"question":["Convert string to <em>array</em>, using ;as delimiter"]}},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_134","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Take off spaces from a string","answer":"$result=trim($input);"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_164","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Regular expression: tabulators and spaces","answer":"[[:space]]"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_160","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Regular expression: 1 or more (not 0)","answer":"+"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_153","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Number returned when comparing a,b","answer":"-1"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_161","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Regular expression : 0, 1 or more","answer":"*"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_158","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Look for string in string, give last position","answer":"$test=strrpos($inputstring,$searchedstring);"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_163","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Regular expression: any lower case letter or dash","answer":"[a-z\\-]"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_165","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Regular expression: word","answer":"\\w"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_157","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Look for string in string, starting from position n","answer":"$test=strpos($inputstring,$searchedstring,n);"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_139","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"format: string of 5 characters","answer":"%5s"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_167","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Regular expression: aa or ab or ac","answer":"aa|ab|ac"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_151","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"From bibula, take ibula","answer":"substr(\"bibula\",1)"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_155","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Get the length of a string","answer":"strlen($inputstring)"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_177","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"get code from mycode.php making sure it is done only once","answer":"include_once('mycode.php');"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_152","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Compare two strings","answer":"strcmp($firstinput,$secondinput) 0 if same >0 if $firststring>$secondstring (or if first string is higher in alphabet than second string)"},{"id":"https___www_vincent_luciani_com_sitemap_xml_170","category":"PHP","subCategory":"Deal with strings","question":"Case insensitive search","answer":"/i"}],"details":{"totalHits":44,"aggregations":{"category":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"PHP","doc_count":44,"subCategory":{"doc_count_error_upper_bound":0,"sum_other_doc_count":0,"buckets":[{"key":"Deal with strings","doc_count":44}]}}]}}}}


const  mockFetch = url => {
    console.log("using mockFetch")
    switch (url) {
        case "firstPage": {
            return pageOne
        }
        case "secondPage": {
            return pageTwo
        }
        case "thirdPage": {
            return pageThree
        }
        case "nothing":{
            return {}
        }
        case "filter":{
            return filteredResult
        }
        default:
        return pageOne;
    }

    
}



export default mockFetch